So, how is the princess going to die?
Two days from now, in the early morning,
while heading from Archen to Sanes Village,
the princess's caravan gets
attacked by a hydra.
The forests near Archen have always
been infested with monsters,
and Sanes Village was attacked
by a hydra a month ago.
The princess has come to Archen
upon learning of it.
And next, she'll head to the
still dangerous Sanes Village,
only to be cut down on the way there.
People will say it's a tragedy
caused by her goodwill and bad luck,
but if you ask me, it's the natural
outcome of her reckless actions.
There was no funny business
behind it, was there?
Like an assassination made to look
like the work of monsters.
Well, following the princess's death,
there were all kinds of rumors.
The most suspicion was cast upon
the princess's half-brother, Prince Carenas.
As a concubine's child,
he's second in line for the throne.
He benefits the most from her death.
And even more suspiciously,
Prince Carenas is in town right now.
Oh? But no one's talking about that.
He's a shut-in and won't make
public appearances.
How very suspicious.
Well, I said there were rumors, but in the end,
it was deemed an unfortunate accident.
And now you're trying to use
that unfortunate accident?
Yeah. I'll gallantly show up to save
Zirgus's pride and joy when she's in danger.
It'll make the perfect start
to my heroic tale.
The key is making it look natural
when I rush in to rescue her,
but I don't even know the exact
location of the hydra attack.
I'll just have to keep an eye on her.
Man, I asked around
about the princess's plans,
but I didn't learn squat.
Why were you looking into that?
Why?
So she and I can have
our fated encounter, of course.
What?
To make it happen, I'm going to gallantly
swoop in when she's in danger, and...
What's up?
Well... I just can't believe
I had the same idea as you.
What?! You did?!
Get in line!
Not like that.
Apparently, the princess really is in danger
according to Sildonia's prophetic ability.
Huh?
Right?
Uh, yeah. Something like that.
Okay! In other words, this is my chance.
So I'll have to follow the princess around.
Good thing I'm great at that!
Keep your pants on.
They're off.
Is it really true that
the princess is in danger?
Yeah, Sildonia's—
It was a prophetic vision.
An ability of yours truly.
But how are we going to follow her?
We can't get too close, can we?
We shall use another one of my abilities.
W-Wait, huh?
What's going on?
She'll follow the carriage as a hawk.
They'll never notice.
My true form is the gemstone in the sword.
This body is an avatar made of magic power,
so it can be easily modified.
Plus...
I can even do this!
Ah, I've spotted the carriage.
She's being escorted by town guards.
I'm sure they have some training,
but we can't count on them.
How incredible.
Use it right, and this is even
more powerful than a good weapon.
Not to mention convenient!
I'm so jealous! You can peep all you want!
On what, exactly?
Don't tell me you spied on us in the bath!
Yeah, no. I tried to, but Kyle got in my way.
You lowlife!
So Urza's secret is still safe, thanks to Kyle.
Huh?
You mean her heart-shaped birthmark?
What?
You! How do you know about that?!
So you did go to peep yourself!
N-No, wait! This is a misunderstanding!
Something strange is happening.
What is it? Is it monsters?
No. In fact...
The drivers have stopped the horses
and attacked the guards.
That's not strange! That's nuts!
Let's head there!
Is it done?
Yeah. Let's hurry.
Haste!
That should do it.
I've got a lot of questions for these guys.
The princess is alive!
She's just unconscious.
These guys may have more friends.
Theron, stay with the princess.
Hellhounds. Lots of them, too.
Oh no!
There are too many of them!
Theron! Can you get the carriage moving?
No. The reins have been cut.
It'll take a while to fix this.
What is that?
I knew it would come.
It's approaching, just as you predicted.
Theron! Princess Milena's safety comes first.
I'm counting on you.
You two, stick with Theron.
You're going to fight it alone?
I won't get reckless.
I've got a shot at beating it.
I figure this is our best option.
Don't die.
Salamander!
It's a little late to be asking,
but you can fell a hydra, right?
Their strength is determined
by their number of heads.
I've beaten one with three heads before.
Huh? Well, that's a lot more than three...
What's the plan? Do we run?
It's too late for that.
You've got eight heads, do you?
Even so... I've gotta do this.
A hydra's moves are straightforward
and easy to read,
but its tough scales make it
practically immune to sword attacks.
And most dangerous of all...
Its poison breath!
However, this dragon leather
armor nullifies the poison.
Blizzard!
Explosion!
Very good. You're putting up
a better fight than I expected.
I came prepared, you know? That said...
It regenerates like crazy.
This thing's a tough opponent.
Oh, come on! There's no end to them!
I'm worried about Kyle.
Can he really fight a hydra alone?
I know, but...
We need to take care of these first.
Damn, they sure are persistent.
That was my last Blizzard stone.
Its regeneration is on another
level from a three-headed hydra.
There's no sign of it weakening.
I'll have to strike at the source.
I can give that a try.
Haste!
Ow...
Nice! It worked!
I see. You shoved Explosion
stones into the wound.
Just throwing them against the hydra
wouldn't have done much damage.
Either way, that strike was quite powerful.
Yeah. That move's all about speed and power.
It leaves me too vulnerable
to use much in real combat.
Anyway, this sure is a gruesome sight.
I know I'm the one who caused it, but still...
We're finally finished!
Yeah.
I'm worried about Kyle. Let's go.
Are you two okay?
Kyle! You're all right?
You actually defeated the hydra alone?
It did give me a little trouble,
but it was no big deal.
You reek!
Huh?
She's right! You do reek!
Really?
You stink of hydra!
Stay away until you get that smell off.
What?
You were hoping for more praise, weren't you?
Shut up.
How's the princess?
She hasn't woken up yet.
Looks like she and her
ladies-in-waiting were drugged.
We should probably
give them antidote potions.
Yeah. Buying some was a good call.
Kyle, I found this on the ground.
It wasn't sealed.
I'd wager the two drivers lured the monsters
here to attack the princess.
In other words, the princess's
death wasn't an accident,
but an assassination made to look like one.
Send a squad.
How is she?
Am I alive?
Don't push yourself too hard yet.
I thought I'd never wake up again.
It would seem my luck hasn't run out yet.
Are you the ones responsible for saving me?
It was me! I saved you!
My name is Kyle Leonard.
While traveling, we happened to see you
under attack by bandits and monsters,
so my friends and I saved you.
Princess Milena!
It's all right, Arka.
These people saved me.
B-But we can't trust such strangers.
Thank you.
If not for you all, we would surely be dead.
Er, Your Highness...
The danger has passed, no?
It has, but... the situation outside is ugly.
I'll be fine.
I must see it for myself.
We're on the road from Archen
to Sanes, are we not?
Y-Yes...
Are all the guards dead?
Yes. By the time we got here,
they were already slain.
She seems pretty different from before.
Yeah.
Kyle.
A group of cavaliers is inbound from Archen.
Princess Milena, part of the
king's guard is headed this way.
Oh no! We must flee this instant!
They won't just kill me,
but all of you as well!
No, I meant from your kingdom.
Won't they defend you?
Defend me? Of course not.
The man who wants me dead
is the captain of the second battalion.
His name is Zentos.
Zentos? You mean that Zentos?
Arka, burn the bodies in the area.
Neas farsokea zirknado...
Fireball!
That man is after my life.
With the corpses scorched, he won't
be able to identify them right away.
We must buy as much time as possible.
Ninos, stay with me. Arka, you'll drive.
We shall clear the area at once.
You should get in as well.
I'll explain the situation.
If we're trying to buy time,
the monsters will help slow them down.
Next Time
Reunion at Dawn
Next time: "Reunion at Dawn."